FELIX CATZN

Software/Web developer

Vancouver, BC

604 9107 682

fcatzin@hotmail.com

https://linkedin.com/in/felix-catzin-74784a138

OBJECTIVE

Apply all the knowledge obtained throughout my past work experiences and autonomy in order the company process to be automated, implementing professional and competitive methods and technics for the purpose of enhance currents or new systems technologies in the company, likewise, offering a professional – company feedback for a mutual growth.

EDUCATION -

UI/UX Design

At Cornerstone International Community College of Canada in Vancouver, BC, Canada. From 2024 to Current

Information & Communication Technologies engineering

At Universidad Tecnologica de Cancún in Mexico.
From 2016 to 2018

(International Exchange) Systems Engineering

At Universidad Tecnologica de Cancún in Mexico. From 2016 to 2018

Information & Communication Technologies engineering

At Universidad Tecnologica de Cancún in Mexico. From 2016 to 2018

EXPERIENCE

September 2020 – January 2024

Developer Specialist • Telcel

- I automated reports with Java to reduce the handmade reports and send them by email.
- I managed & developed the Sign Contract module for a national Android mobile application in order to use less physical paper.
- I developed and managed SOAP & RESTFUL web services.
- Technologies used: Java Spring, Spring boot, Microservices, Oracle Database, Linux command line, Android Studio.

July 2018 - October 2019

PHP Developer • Grupo Humanitta

- I developed an invoice system for payrolls to reduce about 80% of work for the H.R area so they can calculate the payment and taxes easier.
- Technologies used: SQL, PHP OOP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS.

April 2017 – June 2018

C# Developer • Consultoría Dual

- I optimized the ERP modules such as reports and invoice modules so other areas can reduce the time spent on analyzing the data.
- Developed a desktop application for uploading Excel sheets in order to convert raw information to reports.
- Technologies used: C#, Javascript, ASP.NET, Microsoft SQL Server, Transact-SQL programming

August 2016 - March 2017

Web Developer • Vacaciones Cancun

- I designed & developed the site web and landing pages.
- Both the CRM and the landing pages were managed by me.
- I designed many databases to save information from the landing pages.
- Technologies used: PHP, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, MySQL, Team Foundation Server.

KEY SKILLS -

Knowledge

- Web Services
- Micro Services
- Data bases
- SCRUM

Tools

- Android Studio
- Linux
- Java frameworks
- Websphere Application Server
- SVN & GIT repositories

ETHICS

Respect for confidentiality

I ensure the sensitive data are well saved and respect the privacy of them following the company polices.

Professional responsibility

I always make sure to deliver high-quality results.

Continuous improvement

Learning is one of the most valuable ethics I have not only in my work place but also in my life.

Team collaboration

One of the most important keys for a successful project is to collaborate as a team. I enjoy being supportive and collaborative with my teammates.